brainstormlive.com 2011-06-01

# Brainstorm Live

  | Scope  

This notice provides highlights of the full Brainstorm Creative Lab's Online Privacy Statement below. This notice and the full privacy statement apply to those Microsoft Web sites and services that display or link to this notice.  
  
---|---  
  
* * *

  | Personal Information | • | 

When you register for certain Brainstorm Creative Lab's services, we will ask you to provide personal information.  
  
---|---  
• | 

The information we collect may be combined with information obtained from other Brainstorm Creative Lab's services, our partner sites and other companies.  
  
• | 

We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interactions with our sites and services to offer a personalized experience.  
  
        | Your Choices | • | 

You can stop the delivery of promotional e-mail from a Brainstorm Creative Lab's sites or services  by following the instructions in the e-mail you receive.  
  
---|---  
• | 

To make proactive choices about how we communicate with you by e-mail, telephone, and/or postal mail, follow the instructions listed in the Communication Preferences of the full privacy statement.  
  
• | 

To opt-out of the display of personalized advertisements, go to the Display of Advertising section of the full privacy statement.  
  
• | 

To view and edit your personal information, go to the access section of the full privacy statement.  
  
* * *

  | Uses of Information | • | 

We use the information we collect to provide the services you request. Our services may include the display of personalized content and advertising.  
  
---|---  
• | 

We use your information to inform you of other products or services offered by Brainstorm Creative Lab and its affiliates, and to send you relevant survey invitations related to Microsoft services.  
  
• | 

We do not sell, rent, or lease our customer lists to third parties. In order to help provide our services, we occasionally provide information to other companies that work on our behalf.  
  
        | Important Information  
| • | 

The full Brainstorm Creative Lab's Online Privacy Statement below contains links to supplementary information about specific Brainstorm Creative Lab's sites or services.  
  
---|---  
• | 

The sign in credentials (username/e-mail address and password) used to sign in to most Brainstorm Creative Lab's sites and services are part of the Brainstorm Universal Login.  
  
• | 

For more information on how to help protect your personal computer, your personal information and your family online, visit our [online safety resources](http://www.microsoft.com/athome/security/default.mspx).  

|   
  
* * *

  | How to Contact Us  

For more information about our privacy practices, go to the full Brainstorm Creative Lab's Online Privacy Statement below. Or write us using our Web form. If you have a technical or general support question, please feel free to email us at info [@] brainstormcl.com.  
  
---|---  

* * *

**FULL BRAINSTORM CREATIVE LAB'S ONLINE PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Brainstorm Creative Lab is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the Brainstorm Creative Lab Online Privacy Statement below and also any supplemental information listed to the right for additional details about particular Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services that you may use.

This Brainstorm Creative Lab Online Privacy Statement applies to data collected by Brainstorm Creative Lab through the majority of its Web sites and services, as well as its offline product support services. It does not apply to those Brainstorm Creative Lab sites, services and products that do not display or link to this statement or that have their own privacy statements. Some products and services mentioned in this statement may not be available in all markets at this time.

Collection of Your Personal Information

At some Brainstorm Creative Lab sites, we ask you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. If you choose to make a purchase or sign up for a paid subscription service, we will ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address, which is used to create a Brainstorm Creative Lab billing account.

In order to access some Brainstorm Creative Lab services, you will be asked to sign in with an e-mail address and password. Many different Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services use the same credentials which we refer to as your Brainstorm Creative Lab credentials.In order to access some Brainstorm Creative Lab services, you will be asked to sign in with an e-mail address and password, which we refer to as your Brainstorm Creative Lab credentials. You can use the same credentials to sign in to many different Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services, as well as those of select Brainstorm Creative Lab partners. By signing in on one Brainstorm Creative Lab site or service, you may be automatically signed into other Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services. If you access our services via a mobile phone, you may also use your telephone number and a PIN as an alternative credential to your username and password. As part of creating your credentials, you may also be requested to provide questions and secret answers, which we use to help verify your identity and assist in resetting your password, as well as an alternate e-mail address. Some services may require added security, and in these cases, you may be asked to create an additional security key. Finally, a unique ID number will be assigned to your credentials which will be used to identify your credentials and associated information.

We may collect information about your interaction with Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services. For example, we may use Web site analytics tools on our site to retrieve information from your browser, including the site you came from, the search engine(s) and the keywords you used to find our site, the pages you view within our site, your browser add-ons, and your browser's width and height. We may also use technologies, such as cookies and web beacons (described below), to collect information about the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on our sites and services. Additionally, we collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses. We also deliver advertisements (see the Display of Advertising section below) and provide Web site analytics tools on non-Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services, and we may collect information about page views on these third party sites as well.

When you receive newsletters or promotional e-mail from Brainstorm Creative Lab, we may use web beacons (described below), customized links or similar technologies to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you click in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information.

In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with Brainstorm Creative Lab, information collected through one Brainstorm Creative Lab service may be combined with information obtained through other Brainstorm Creative Lab services. We may also supplement the information we collect with information obtained from other companies. For example, we may use services from other companies that enable us to derive a general geographic area based on your IP address in order to customize certain services to your geographic area.

Use of Your Personal Information

Brainstorm Creative Lab collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and services. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences. For more information about the use of information for advertising, see the Display of Advertising section below.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. Some Brainstorm Creative Lab services may send periodic member letters that are considered part of the service. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other Brainstorm Creative Lab products and services, and/or share your personal information with Brainstorm Creative Lab partners so they may send you information about their products and services.

Personal information collected on Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Brainstorm Creative Lab or its affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers maintain facilities. Brainstorm Creative Lab abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union, the European Economic Area, and Switzerland.

Sharing of Your Personal Information

Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of Brainstorm Creative Lab and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent. Some Brainstorm Creative Lab sites allow you to choose to share your personal information with select Brainstorm Creative Lab partners so that they can contact you about their products, services or offers. Other sites, such as brainstormlive.com, do not share your contact information with third parties for marketing purposes, but instead may give you a choice as to whether you wish to receive communications from Brainstorm Creative Lab on behalf of external business partners about a partner's particular offering (without transferring your personal information to the third party). See the Communication Preferences section below for more information.

Some Brainstorm Creative Lab services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both Brainstorm Creative Lab and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. However, for credit card processing, our fraud detection vendors may use aggregate data to help improve their service. This helps them more accurately detect fraudulent uses of credit cards. We may access or disclose information about you, including the content of your communications, in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of Brainstorm Creative Lab or our customers, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of the services; or (c) act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of Brainstorm Creative Lab employees, customers or the public. We may also disclose personal information as part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets.

Accessing Your Personal Information

You may have the ability to view or edit your personal information online. In order to help prevent your personal information from being viewed by others, you will be required to sign in with your credentials (e-mail address and password). The appropriate method(s) for accessing your personal information will depend on which sites or services you have used.

Brainstorm Creative Lab.com - You can access and update your profile on Brainstorm Creative Lab.com by visiting the Brainstorm Creative Lab.com Profile Center.

Brainstorm Creative Lab Billing and Account Services - If you have a Brainstorm Creative Lab Billing account, you can add to or update your information at the Brainstorm Creative Lab Billing Web site by clicking on the "Personal Information" or "Billing Information" links.

Brainstorm Creative Lab Connect - If you are a registered user of Brainstorm Creative Lab Connect, you can access and edit your personal information by clicking Manage Your Connect Profile at the Brainstorm Creative Lab Connect Web site.

Public Profile - If you have created a public profile, you may also edit or delete information in your public profile by going to the Member Directory.

Keyword Advertising - If you buy Keyword advertising, you can review and edit your personal information at the Brainstorm Creative Lab adCenter Web site.

Brainstorm Creative Lab Partner Programs - If you are registered with Brainstorm Creative Lab Partner Programs, you can review and edit your profile by clicking Manage Your Account on the Partner Program Web site.

Some Brainstorm Creative Lab sites or services may collect personal information that is not accessible via the links above. However, in such cases, you may be able to access that information through alternative means of access described by the service. Or you can write us by using our Web form, and we will contact you within 30 days regarding your request.

Communication Preferences

You can stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive.

You may also have the option of proactively making choices about the receipt of promotional e-mail, telephone calls, and postal mail from particular Brainstorm Creative Lab sites or services by visiting and signing into the following pages:

The Brainstorm Creative Lab.com Profile Center allows you to choose whether you wish to receive marketing communications from Brainstorm Creative Lab.com, to select whether Brainstorm Creative Lab.com may share your contact information with selected third parties, and to subscribe or unsubscribe to newsletters about our products and services.

If you have an Xbox.com or Xbox Live account, you can set your contact preferences and choose whether to share your contact information with Xbox partners on the My Xbox page on Xbox.com or on your console by selecting Privacy Settings under Edit Gamer Profile on Xbox 360, or selecting the Info Sharing option in Account Management on the Original Xbox Live dashboard.

If you are registered with Brainstorm Creative Lab Partner Programs, you can set your contact preferences or choose to share your contact information with other Brainstorm Creative Lab partners by clicking Manage Your Account on the Partner Program Web site.

If you have a Zune account or a Zune Pass subscription, you can set your contact preferences and choose whether to share your contact information with Zune partners at Zune.net (click Manage My Account, Newsletter Options from your profile page) or through the Zune software (sign in, click your Zune tag, then click My Account, Newsletter Options to go to the appropriate page at Zune.net).

To manage your preferences or update your contact information, please sign in to your Brainstorm Creative Lab adCenter or Brainstorm Creative Lab pubCenter account, or contact your account team. If you advertise with Brainstorm Creative Lab Advertising and would like to update your preferences, please contact your account team.

To manage your Brainstorm Creative Lab Advertising preferences or update your contact information, please sign in to your Brainstorm Creative Lab adCenter or Brainstorm Creative Lab pubCenter account, or contact your account team. If you advertise with Brainstorm Creative Lab Advertising and would like to update your preferences, please contact your account team.

These choices do not apply to the display of online advertising. Nor do they apply to the receipt of mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain Brainstorm Creative Lab services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service.

Display of Advertising (Opt-Out)

Many of the Web sites and online services we offer, as well as those of our partners, are supported by advertising. Through the Brainstorm Creative Lab Advertising Platform, we may display ads on our own sites and the sites of our advertising partners.

When we display online advertisements to you, we will place a one or more persistent cookies on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time we display an ad to you. The cookies we use for advertising have an expiry date of no more than 2 years. Because we may serve advertisements on many different Web sites, we are able to compile information over time about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements we display. We use this information to make predictions about your characteristics, interests or preferences and to display targeted advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also associate this information with your subsequent visit, purchase or other activity on participating advertisers’ Web sites in order to determine the effectiveness of the advertisements.

While we may use some of the information we collect in order to personalize the ads we show you, we designed our systems to select ads based only on data that does not personally and directly identify you. For example, we may select the ads we display according to certain general interest categories or segments that we have inferred based on (a) demographic or interest data, including any you may have provided when creating an account (e.g. age, zip or postal code, gender), demographic or interest data acquired from other companies, and a general geographic location derived from your IP address, (b) the pages you view and links you click when using Brainstorm Creative Lab’s and its advertising partners’ Web sites and services, and (c) the search terms you enter when using Brainstorm Creative Lab’s Internet search services, such as Bing, and (d) information about the users you most frequently interact with through Brainstorm Creative Lab’s communications or social networking services, such as Messenger. For more information about how we target ads, visit Personalized Advertising from Brainstorm Creative Lab.

When we display personalized targeted ads, we take a number of steps designed to protect your privacy. For example, we store page views, clicks and search terms used for ad personalization targeting separately from your contact information or other data that directly identifies you (such as your name, e-mail address, etc.). Further, we have built in technological and process safeguards designed to prevent the unauthorized correlation of this data. We also give you the ability to opt-out of personalized targeted ads. For more information or to use the opt-out feature, you may visit our opt-out page. In addition, you can go to the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt-out of ad targeting from member companies.

Although the majority of the online advertisements on Brainstorm Creative Lab sites are displayed by Brainstorm Creative Lab, we also allow third-party ad serving companies, including other ad networks, to display advertisements on our sites. These companies currently include, but are not limited to: 24/7 Real Media, aCerno,Inc, AdBlade, AdConion, AdFusion, Advertising.com, Bane Media, Brand.net, CasaleMedia, Collective Media, Fox Interactive, Interclick, Millennial, PrecisionClick, ROI Media, Social Media, SpecificMedia, TrafficMarketplace, Tribal Fusion, ValueClick, and YuMe.

These companies may offer you a way to opt-out of ad targeting based on their cookies, and some of them are also members of the Network Advertising Initiative. You may find more information by clicking on the company names above and following the links to the Web sites of each company.

Security of Your Personal Information

Brainstorm Creative Lab is committed to protecting the security of your personal information and information collected for advertising purposes. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

Collection and Use of Children's Personal Information

Many Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services are intended for general audiences and do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. When a Brainstorm Creative Lab site does collect age information, and users identify themselves as under 13, the site will either block such users from providing personal information, or will seek to obtain consent from parents for the collection, use and sharing of their children's personal information. We will not knowingly ask children under the age of 13 to provide more information than is reasonably necessary to provide our services.

Please note that if you grant consent for your child to use Brainstorm Creative Lab services, this will include such general audience communication services as e-mail, instant messaging, and online groups, and your child will be able to communicate with, and disclose personal information to, other users of all ages. Parents can change or revoke the consent choices previously made, and review, edit or request the deletion of their children's personal information.

We encourage you to talk with your children about communicating with strangers and disclosing personal information online. You and your child can visit our online safety resources for additional information about using the Internet safely.

Use of Cookies

Brainstorm Creative Lab Web sites use "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to these sites. Brainstorm Creative Lab Web sites also use cookies as described in the Collection of your Information and Display of Advertising sections of this privacy statement.

When you sign in to a site using your Brainstorm Creative Lab credentials, we store your unique ID number, and the time you signed in, in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. This cookie allows you to move from page to page at the site without having to sign in again on each page. When you sign out, these cookies are deleted from your computer. We also use cookies to improve the sign in experience. For example, your e-mail address may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie allows your e-mail address to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. If you are using a public computer or do not otherwise want this information to be stored, you can select the appropriate radio button on the sign-in page, and this cookie will not be used.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Brainstorm Creative Lab sites and services that depend on cookies, and some advertising preferences that are dependent on cookies may not be able to be respected.

If you choose to accept cookies, you also have the ability to later delete cookies that you have accepted. In Internet Explorer 7, you can delete cookies by selecting “Tools”, “Delete browsing history” and clicking the “Delete Cookies” button. If you choose to delete cookies, any settings and preferences controlled by those cookies, including advertising preferences, will be deleted and may need to be recreated.

Use of Web Beacons

Brainstorm Creative Lab Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that may be used to assist in delivering cookies on our sites and allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Brainstorm Creative Lab may also employ Web beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns or other operations of our sites. We prohibit Web beacons on our sites from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information.

Finally, we may work with other companies that advertise on Brainstorm Creative Lab sites to place Web beacons on their sites in order to allow us to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement on a Brainstorm Creative Lab site results in a purchase or other action on the advertiser's site.

Controlling Unsolicited E-mail ("Spam")

Brainstorm Creative Lab is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial e-mail, or "spam." Brainstorm Creative Lab has a strict Anti-Spam Policy prohibiting the use of any Brainstorm Creative Lab-provided e-mail account and or messaging service to send spam. Brainstorm Creative Lab will not sell, lease or rent its e-mail subscriber lists to third parties. While Brainstorm Creative Lab continues to actively review and implement new technology, such as expanded filtering features, there is no currently available technology that will totally prevent the sending and receiving of unsolicited e-mail. Using junk e-mail tools and being cautious about the sharing of your e-mail address while online will help reduce the amount of unsolicited e-mail you receive.

Enforcement of This Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact us by using our Web form. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with Brainstorm Creative Lab to resolve your concerns.

Changes to This Privacy Statement

We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. If there are material changes to this statement or in how Brainstorm Creative Lab will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Brainstorm Creative Lab is protecting your information.
